hello we are creating a technology
cooperative that is owned and operated
by us the user with a mission to make
life better we are gonna run it like
never before with full transparency and
democracy we are going to use it to
create the lives that work for us as
individuals in this series of videos
that I will be releasing daily over the
next couple weeks I'm going to cover how
technology is powerful yet creating it
is risky
I will also be covering how when we do
it together it is not only more powerful
but less risky and therein lies the
potential of a technology cooperative I
will be covering what tools we will need
for massive collaboration as well as
what we can then create with those tools
for massive collaboration I will be
covering how you as an individual can
get involved if this project calls to
you so please like and subscribe and hit
that little bell so you will be notified
over the next couple of weeks when I
release the videos daily and come help
create a better world thank you